Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public relations and graphics records circa 1942-2009 COR0003.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public relations and graphics records
circa 1942-2009
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
COR0003.3.RG
241.5 Linear Feet
Although the Corcoran had no formal public relations office until 1961 the large number of clipping scrapbooks bear witness to the interest of the press in Corcoran activities. Prior to 1961 most publicity efforts were directed by the Director's Office or the Curatorial Office. The Public Relations records show the activities of the Gallery's Public Relations Office in publicizing and promoting the activities of the Gallery. The most helpful records for researchers include the press clippings scrapbooks (these should be used in conjunction with the Special Exhibitions Scrapbooks).
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open to research.
When conducting research within The Corcoran Archives collections, please be advised of the following exceptions:
Records of the Board of Trustees (RG 1.0) and records of the Office of the Director (RG 2.0) are closed to research for 25 years from the date of creation.
Development records are closed to research (RG 3.2).
Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for the lifetime of the student, and are presumed to be open 75 years after the date of record creation (RG 9.0 Series 4).
Personnel and financial records are closed for 50 years from date of record creation (RG 4.0).
Please see the Public Services and Instruction Librarian for assistance.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Corcoran Institution Board of Trustees donated these records to The George Washington University in 2016.
Arrangement
Organized into 14 series: Exhibition files [legacy series]; Exhibition files; Event files [legacy series]; Event files; Administrative records [legacy series]; Administrative records; Budget records [legacy series]; Press releases [legacy series]; Press and publicity; Clipping scrapbooks [legacy series]; Audio visual materials; Design records; Graphics; and Suzan Reed Weaver publication files.
Historical narrative
The first section of this history, covering events through 1981, was prepared by Corcoran Archivist Katherine M. Kovocs for publication in 1985 with the support of the National Endowment for the Humanities.
Although the Corcoran had no formal public relations office until 1961 the large number of clipping scrapbooks bear witness to the interest of the press in Corcoran activities. Prior to 1961 most publicity efforts were directed by the Director's Office or the Curatorial Office. With the expansion of the Gallery's outreach activities in the early 1960s Mrs. Inga Wall Heck joined the Gallery's staff and established, along with her other responsibilities, the first professional public relations office at the Corcoran.
The office sends out press releases on exhibitions, special events and Gallery and School activities, and works with the press and broadcast media in the promotion of Gallery activities. In 1978 the Board of Trustees established a Public Relations Committee with J. Burke Wilkinson as Chairman. This Committee lends the help, advice and prestige of the Board of Trustees to the Gallery's public relations activities. In 1981, the Trustees formed a Public Relations Advisory Committee made up of individuals involved in the media and the community to help increase attendance at the Treasures of Ancient Nigeria, P.H. Polk, and Black Folk Art in America exhibition. Because of their efforts and those of the Public Relations staff, attendance was spectacular for these exhibitions. In 1979, the promotion of the Daumier in Retrospect, 1808-1879 exhibition received several media awards.
The following section of this history was prepared in 2019 by George Washington University SCRC staff with the support of the Luce Foundation.
The Department expanded its responsibilities in the 1980s, partially taking over graphic design from the Education Department. This lead the office to take a more active role in directly creating content to be provided to outlets for promotion of the Gallery and School. They also took on greater involvement in creation of in-gallery promotional content, advertising campaigns, and general advertising materials.
The office took on management of the Gallery's web presence in the 1990s. The original website is still available to view, as well as archived versions on the Internet Archive Wayback Machine.
In the 2000s, the office turned its attention towards creating a consistent style guide for the Gallery. This included color, font, sizing and branding consistency for the Gallery, the school, and all outreach and advertising materials.
Custodial History
The Public Relations (PR) Records of the Corcoran Gallery of Art were transferred to the Archives from the PR Office and various storage areas from 1980 to 2016.
Scope and Contents
The Public Relations records show the activities of the Gallery's Public Relations Office in publicizing and promoting the activities of the Gallery. The most helpful records for researchers include the press clippings scrapbooks (these should be used in conjunction with the Special Exhibitions Scrapbooks Record Group 5, Series 7 and the history clipping file). This should not be considered an exhaustive account of the Corcoran's appearance in print because for most years the Gallery did not subscribe to a clipping service. In addition the PR exhibition files should be used in conjunction with the Curatorial exhibition files to learn the extent of media and press interest in a particular exhibition. The Press Releases in Series 5 give succinct descriptions of exhibitions and events and are especially helpful when only a short explanation of a particular event or exhibition is needed. Perusal of the press release series will also give the researcher an overall impression the kinds of activities during a particular time period.
Separated Materials
During processing in 1984 the following materials were removed from the PR records and placed in more appropriate locations:
Photographs moved to Archives Audio-Visual Records Newspaper clippings moved to Artist vertical files or history clipping files Announcements/Invitations moved to Special Events ephemera Exhibition catalogs (Corcoran) moved to Curatorial Publications Exhibition catalogs (non-Corcoran) moved to School Library
- Exhibition files [legacy series], 1961-1962; Series 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence and memorandum concerning the promotion of Gallery exhibitions.
  - Norwegian Show (Releases), 1961 October 5-1961 November 5; Series 1 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - German Expressionist Paintings from the Mr. and Mrs. Morton D. May Collection (non-Corcoran releases), 1962 May 28-June 30; Series 1 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - German Expressionist Paintings (Correspondence, Memos, and releases), 1962 May 28-June 30; Series 1 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - 27th Biennial Correspondence, 1961 January 14-February 26; Series 1 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - 27th Biennial Releases & Correspondence, 1961 January 14-February 26; Series 1 (Box 161, Folder 5)
- Exhibition files, 1944-2009; 1983-2009; Series 11
  Arrangement
  Folders have been maintained in the order received when transferred to GW.
  This series contains records that detail the work of the Corcoran Gallery of Art public relations and graphics division of the Corcoran Gallery of Art. These records date from 1944-2009 with the bulk dates between 1983-2009.
  - Typologies -- Press Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Typologies -- Credit Line, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Typologies -- Glossies, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Typologies -- Press Preview, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Typologies -- Press Clips, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hutty -- Fact Sheet, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alfred Hutty Checklist, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alfred Hutty Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alfred Hutty Clips, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alfred Hutty Background, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alfred Hutty Glossies, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Kiki / Zizi Images, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Kiki Smith Zizi Raymond, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Kiki Zizi -- Press Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Kiki Zizi -- Fact Sheet, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Kiki Zizi -- Checklist, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Kiki Smith Zizi Raymond, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Kiki Zizi -- Visuals, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Kiki Zizi -- Clips, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - William T. Wiley - Exhibition Event, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - William T. Wiley - Press Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - William T. Wiley - Background, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - William T. Wiley - Checklist, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Wiley Checklist, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - William Wiley, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - William T. Wiley - Events, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - William T. Wiley - Fact Sheet, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - William Wiley Press Clips, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Wiley - The Good and the Grubby Part Strait, 1985, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Wiley - Opening Closing, 1978-1988; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Wiley - Agent Orange, 1983; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - William Wiley Catalogue, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Joyce Scott -- Fact Sheet, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Joyce Scott -- Press Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Joyce Scott -- Checklist, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Joyce Scott -- Background, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Joyce Scott -- Press Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Joyce Scott, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Joyce Scott -- Press Preview, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Buddah Gives Basketball to the Ghetto, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Necklace Party (South African...), Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Big Mama, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Max Weber -- Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Max Weber -- Artist Bio, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Max Weber -- Checklist, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Max Weber -- Program Fact Sheets, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Max Weber -- Visuals, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Max Weber -- Images, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - CGA News Folders, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Tony Cragg, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Tony Cragg -- Checklist, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Tony Cragg -- Press Release, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Tony Cragg -- Media List, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Tony Cragg -- Press Clippings, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Rauschenberg -- Originals, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Rauschenberg Press Availability, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Rauschenberg Program, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Rauschenberg Itinerary, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Rauschenberg Fact Sheet, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - [Newport Harbor Art Museum], Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Rauschenberg Press Release, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Robert Rauschenberg Correspondence, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mary Lynn Kotz Release -- Rausch.., Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Rauschenberg Opening Lists, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Rauschenberg Black and White Glossies, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Robert Rauschenberg Checklist, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Rauschenberg Black and White Glossies Not Used in Show, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Rauschenberg Color Slides, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rauschenberg Catalogue Copy, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Rauschenberg Film Odyssey Document, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Rauschenberg CBS Sunday a.m. Script, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Rauschenberg Dinner Guest List, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Rauschenberg -- Clippings, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Robert Rauschenberg, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Congressional List, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 42nd Biennial -- Advance Release, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 42nd Biennial -- Catalogue Galleys, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - [42nd Biennial -- Checklist], Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 42nd Biennial -- Internegs, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 42nd Biennial -- PSA, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 42nd Biennial -- Press Preview, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Biennial Mailing Lists -- PressKits, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Sabina Ott Mater Rosa #1, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - L.C. Armstrong Brownout, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Lari Pittman Transcendental and Needy, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Nancy Chun China II: Han Dynasty.., Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Thomas Eric Stanton Tree of Life (Hannibal), Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Irene Pijon The Ganges at Benares, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Judy Mannarino Optics View, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Soviet Photo - Checklist, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Soviet Photography Correspondence, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Soviet Photography Originals for Prerss Kit, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Changing Reailty - Release, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Soviet Photography -- Bios, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Soviet Photo -- Starwood Release, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Soviet Photo -- Preliminary Itinerary, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Soviet Photography -- Press Preview, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Soviet Photo -- ASI Preview List, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Changing Reality: Recent Soviet Phot., Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Soviet Photography - Events, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - B/W - Glossies Soviett Photography, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Yuri Rybtchinski, Prison for Youthful Offenders, 1978; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Rifkhat Yakupov, series Disappearing Village, 1990; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Ljalja Kuznetsova, series Gypsies, 1979; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Igor Moukhin, series The City, 1986; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Soviet Photography -- Negatives, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Calendar of Events, 1990; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - 20 Glossy Reproductions - Soviet Exhibition, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - WGMS "Taste of Washington", Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Music From Washington WETA/MES, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - WLTT - Special Programs, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - WGMS FM, Circa 1990-1992; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Stovall Fact Sheet (Empty), Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Lou Stovall Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Lou Stovall Background, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - [Public Affairs Releases/Exhibition Schedule], 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - [The Realms of Forms as the Object of Knowledge], Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - [Photographs and 42nd Biennial Fact Sheets], 1991; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 42nd Biennial - Background, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 42nd Biennial - Fact Sheet, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 42nd Biennial - Participating Artists, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 42nd Biennial - Programs, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 42nd Biennial - Checklists, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 42nd Biennial - Press Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 42nd Biennial - Clips, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - [Photographs], Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Guillermo Kuitca - Press Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Guillermo Kuitca - Checklist, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Guillermo Kuitca - Fact Sheet, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Guillermo Kuitca - Background, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - [Guillermo Kuitca - Fact Sheet], Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Interface - National Building Museum Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Interface - Program Fact Sheets, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Interface - Checklist, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Interface - Press Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Interface - Sponsor Sheet, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - [Interface - Public Affairs], Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Interface Opening Party, 1992 May 20; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - [Fact Sheets], Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Interface - Advertising, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - [Photographs and Programming for Interface], Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - [Quilt Information], Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - [Pelligrin: Press Kit Originals], Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - [Pelligrin: Background Material, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Pellegrin: Press Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Pellegrin: Fact Sheet, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Pellegrin: Checklist, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Pellegrin: Catalogues, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Pellegrin: Press Preview, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Pellegrin: Glossies, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - [Pellegrin: Fact Sheets], Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Pellegrin: Press Clips, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Sebastiao Salgado Press Clips, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - [San Fransisco Musuem of Modern Art], Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Salgado - Press Release, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Salgado - Checklist, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Salgado - Press Clippings, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - [The New York Times Magazine and Photographs], 1991; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Salgado - Wall Text, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Salgado - Press Preview, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Salgado - Ritchin Essay, Circa 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - [Photography Good Inventions and The New Yorker], 1991; Series 11 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Sport in Art - Background Materials, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Sport inn Art - Press Preview, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Sport in Art - IBM Release, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Sport in Art - Checklist, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Sport in Art - Programs Release, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sport in Art - Press Release, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sport in Art - PSAs, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Indiana Clippings, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sport in Art - Images, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Andy Warhol Kareem Abdul Jabbar, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Thomas Eakins The Wrestlers, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Paul Cadmus Aspects of Suburban Life, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Winslow Homer Croquet Match, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Alex Coville Skater, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Sport in Art - Internegs 8x11, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Magazines, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Newspapers, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Sport in Art - IBM Advertising, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - [IBM The Arts: Fact Sheet], Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Robert Rauschenberg: The Early 1950s, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Corcoran Fact Sheet, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Corcoran Fact Sheet, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Roci Rauschenberg Overseas Culture Interchange, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Robert Rauschenberg: The Early 1950s, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Early Works By Robert Rauschenberg Original, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Corcoran Fact Sheet, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Rauschenberg Mary Lynn Kotz, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - [Helen Dudar: The artist who wants to embrace the whole world], Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - CGA News, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Berenice Abbott, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Berenice Abbott -- Release, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Berenice Abbott Checklist, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Berenice Abbott -- Catalogues, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Berenice Abbott -- Itinerary, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Berenice Abbott - Press Preview, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Berenice Abbott -- Press Clippings, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Berenice Abbott -- Checklist Materials, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Berenice Abbott -- Photographs, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - A Shining Opportunity At The Toledo Museum of Art, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Berenice Abbott Photographer: A Modern Vision, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Soviet Photography - Clippings, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Arena Stage, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - CGA Fact Sheet, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - CGA Fact Sheet, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - CGA Fact Sheet, Circa 1991; Series 11 (Box 5, Folder 46)